Dead is just a word.
Black Phone 2 is a horror, thriller film directed by Scott Derrickson.
Four years after escaping The Grabber, Finney Blake is
struggling with his life after captivity.
When his sister Gwen begins receiving calls in her dreams from the black phone and seeing disturbing visions of three boys being stalked at a winter camp, the siblings
become determined to solve the mystery and confront a killer who has grown more powerful in death and more significant to them than either could imagine.
Finn, played by Mason Thames.
Gwen, played by Madeleine McGraw.
The Grabber, played by Ethan Hawke.
Ernesto, played by Miguel Mora.
Mando, played by Demián Bichir.
Terrence, played by Jeremy Davies.
Black Phone 2 is a 2025 American supernatural horror film
directed by Scott Derrickson who co-wrote it with C.
Robert Cargill.
It serves as a sequel to The Black Phone (2021), is the second feature film
and third overall installment in the Black Phone franchise.
The film stars Mason Thames, Madeleine McGraw, Jeremy Davies, and Ethan Hawke reprising
their roles from the first film, with Demián Bichir also joining the cast.
The story sees siblings Finney and Gwen, along with their friend Ernesto, head to a winter youth camp to uncover a
mystery regarding the first victims of the Grabber, whose ghostly presence now haunts the camp.
Black Phone 2 premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 20, 2025, and was
released in the United States by Universal Pictures on October 17.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and has
grossed $132 million worldwide with a budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of mask, child abuse,
dreams, sibling relationship, winter.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.